techbuzzonline.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Tech Buzz Online

**Tech Buzz Online  **team respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. This privacy policy details how we manage your personal information and safeguard your privacy.

This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use our websites and/or our application software.

We may publish updates to our policy from time to time in which case we will be updating this page along with the date from which the policy is effective from. You should check this page to ensure that you are happy with the changes.

This policy is effective from  _20th Jan 2017_. If you have any concerns about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.techbuzzonline.com/contact/).

 **What we collect**

We  _may_  collect the following information:

  * geographic information including country of residence
  * technical computer and network information such as IP address, device specification, and usage metrics

 **What we do with the information we gather**

We use this information to understand our customers’ needs and provide them with a better product and service. In particular for the following reasons:

  * identify usage trends to improve the product experience
  * analyze error and crash reports to improve application reliability
  * gather feedback on the product’s user experience for future enhancements
  * display targeted advertising that is relevant to your interests

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we employ industry-standard physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **The following policies apply to websites hosted on our domain/subdomains:**

 **Analytics and Log files**

Like many other Web sites, techbuzzonline.com makes use of log files and analytics. The information includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Storage**

We use cookies and web storage to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads to users on techbuzzonline.com based on their visit to techbuzzonline.com and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of these cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on techbuzzonline.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. techbuzzonline.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

By using TechBuzzOnline.com you accept our cookies and agree to our privacy policy. Accept [Learn More](https://www.techbuzzonline.com/privacy-policy/)
